# **Chasani Douglas**

Well-rounded professional Fullstack Engineer focusing in AngularIs and Ruby on Rails with 7 years of web development experience. Developed in agile environments where teamwork and communication were imperative in accomplishing deadlines.

624 Cambridge St. Allston, MA 02134 (845) 820-1750 chasanid@gmail.com www.cjdouglas.com www.linkedin.com/in/chasani

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Gamer Sensei**, Boston, MA— Full Stack Developer

March 2016 - Present

Helped Gamer Sensei grow over 15 times by having a strong hand in the speccing and developing of major site improvements such as Gamer Sensei's complete redesign, virtual currency system, and user dashboard portals. Refined recurring workflows including the Git flow, production deployments to Heroku, and interviewing/onboarding new hires.

## **ESPN, Inc.,** Bristol, CT— Web Developer I

June 2012 - October 2015

Front End Developer creating APIs for in-house and third party applications, such as espn.com and the ESPN app. In charge of emergency maintence of the APIs once a week every month. Quickly became proficient in Groovy, Bootstrap, AngularJs and a proprietary language named Tea as demanded for the job.

## **University of Hartford,** West Hartford, CT— Web Developer

April 2011 - May 2013

Develop, design, and maintain the following websites for the Admissions Department at the University of Hartford: Winter-term, Summer-term, and Paralegal. In charge of training the next hire.

## **University of Hartford,** West Hartford, CT— Tutor

August 2010 - May 2013

In charge of monitoring the computer lab while assisting students with their school work.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **University of Hartford,** West Hartford, CT— B.A.

August 2009 - May 20-13

Multimedia Web Design and Development with a specialization in Human Computer Interaction - Division I Athlete

#### **Front End Technologies**

**Javascript** 

AngularJs

**JQuery** 

**Ajax** 

**JSON** 

HTML 5

**Responsive CSS3** 

Bourbon/Neat

**SCSS** 

**Bootstrap** 

### **Backend Technologies**

Ruby on Rails 4/5

Git/GitHub

OOP

SOL

**Postgres** 

MySQL

**RESTful APIs** 

Development/Docs

#### **AWARDS**

**Junior Achievement Award in** 

Web Development-

University of Hartford

Dean's List (4 Years)-

University of Hartford

**UH Presidential Scholarship-**

University of Hartford